Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vanithavatti-0a227630 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
.NET
SSRS
Microsoft CRM

Vanitha Vatti

Microsoft Dynamics 365 Lead Washington DC-Baltimore Area

Summary

Over 18+ years of Microsoft CRM / D365 experience in Analysis, Design, Development, Customization, Maintenance, testing and implementation of Microsoft Dynamics 365 (CRM). Proven Strong experience in all Microsoft Dynamics CRM versions (Dynamics 365, CRM 2016, CRM 2015, 2013, 2011, CRM4.0 AND CRM1.0). Experienced in Online and On-premises environments, and working in CRM since - CRM1.0 Beta version to Dynamics 365.

I have leveraged my experience in the best possible way in each of my roles. My deep knowledge and experience of Dynamics CRM will be asset for any organization.

I performed various roles: Solutions Architect /Technical Architect, CRM Lead, Admin and developer.

My responsibilities: gathering requirements, configurating solutions, implementation, deployments, training users and working closely with management to expand the technology department. Experienced in various add-ons to CRM.

Experience

Fairfax County Government Microsoft Dynamics 365 Lead April 2020 - Present (5 months)

American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO)
Dynamics 365 Lead
July 2016 - March 2020 (3 years 9 months)
Virginia

Worked as Microsoft Dynamics 365 development lead and acting as solutions Architect: Responsible for system maintenance, performance, and ongoing development work, refresh/upgrades including Unified Interface, core implementations and deployments. Designed architecture for home grown

modules like customer service, OKTA configuration with CRM and custom modules and many integrations. Full hands on experience with CRM system design/development and managing vendor solutions. CRM Mentor for IT and Business teams. Also participated in Data governance, providing good practices and upcoming changes in CRM. And over seeing vendor implementations and providing best options suitable for ASCO needs. CRM goto person for IT, business teams and Vendors. Solved CRM related issues 100% which came to my attention and always look at issues in 360 angle before providing solutions.

Booz Allen Hamilton Microsoft Dynamics CRM Solutions Architect August 2015 - July 2016 (1 year)

Worked as Solutions Architect to oversee 9 CRM projects and teams. And provided high quality solutions to the products and performed code reviews and implementations.

SAIC

CRM Techincal Architect
May 2012 - August 2015 (3 years 4 months)
Chantily, Virginia

Worked for USDA RMA Project: Implemented CRM 2011 & 2015 versions and provided solutions for various business requirements for the project. Acted as techincal architect and lead for the team. Go to person for different departments needs in RMA project. Complete hands on experience with different components of CRM.

PANDORA Jewelry LLC Microsoft Dynamics CRM Lead January 2012 - May 2012 (5 months) Columbia, Maryland

Responsibilities include gathering requirements, building a solution, training users and working closely with management to expand the technology department.

Wells Fargo
Microsoft CRM Solutions Consultant
June 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 7 months)
Columbia. MD

Protech Associates
Senior Microsoft CRM Developer
March 2002 - June 2010 (8 years 4 months)

Worked on various web based technologies, and expert in Microsoft CRM (from version 1 to version 4.0) and SQL.

suported upto 30 clients CRM implementations and upgrades

Aleaf Solutions
Frontend Web Developer
June 2000 - December 2001 (1 year 7 months)

Education

Osmania University

Masters in computer science